Guide to the National Grange of the Patrons of Husbandry records, 1842-1994
National Grange of the Patrons of Husbandry records, 1842-1994
- Series IX. Public Relations Director, C. W. ("Jack") Jackson
  - Community Service Contest - 1958 releases and correspondence (Box 21, Folder 11 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, notes, lists, news clipping, news releases. Includes W. C. "Tom" Sawyer, William Whitsitt, Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge, Sears, Roebuck and Co.
  - Community Service Contest - 1958 - General Information, 1957, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 12 (a-e))
    Correspondence, memos, biographies, scripts, lists (winners and judges), guidebook.
  - Community Service Contest Releases - 1959, 1958, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Reports, summary, memo, releases.
  - Miscellaneous Conferences, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Reports, program, draft, press releases.
  - Confidential memos, pamphlet, 1959, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 21, Folder 16 (a-e))
    Correspondence, pamphlets, statement, certificate.
  - Cross-Country TV, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, news release, script. Correpondence includes Ruth L. Ratny.
  - Jerome Davis, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 18 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, news clipping, addresses, facts, biography, photo.
  - Dedication - Grange Building, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 19 (a, b, c))
    Lists, memos, notes, carbon, correspondence, news releases, program, invitation.
  - Deputy Letter, 1958, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    Memos, letter, newsletters.
  - Expense Account - 1960, Jack Jackson, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 21 (a, b, c))
  - Executive Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 22 (a-f))
    Notes, minutes, memo, agenda, correspondence, statement, outline, report.
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, news clippings, tear sheet.
  - Report on Executive Committee Meeting - Week of Apr. 25, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee Meeting - Week of Apr. 25, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 25 (a, b))
    Correspondence, tear sheet, advertisement. Includes Morris R. Kershner, Wyoming State Grange.
  - Extension Rules, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Fair-Booth Information, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    Suggestions, pamphlet, photograph, correspondence, memo.
  - Farm Fact Kits, 1958-1960 (Box 21, Folder 28 (a-g))
    Correspondence, pamphlets, photocopy, news clipping, lists. Correspondence includes Stuart Symington, Hubert H. Humphrey, Maurice H. Bond, Committee on Agriculture and Forestry: United States Senate, Cornell University.
  - Farm Facts - 1959, 1958, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 29 (a-e))
    News clippings, tear sheets, addresses, report, pamphlets, script, correspondence.
  - Farm Facts - 1960, 1959, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 30 (a, b))
    Papers, address, release, pamphlets, correspondence.
  - Farm Program Philosophy, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    Summary, statement, address, report and revision, draft.
  - Flemming Fan Club, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    Memo, report.
  - Seward Foote, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, biography, plan and outline, report.
  - Community Service Contest - 1959 (Box 21, Folder 34 (a-g))
    Memos, pamphlet, newsletters, statistics, reports, correspondence, lists, itinerary, programs, agenda, notes, minutes, telegrams, release, news clipping. Includes William Whitsitt, Helen Henley, Sears, Roebuck and Co., Christian Science Monitor.
  - General Promotion, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, plan, pamphlets, chart.
  - Grange Activities Extend Around the Globe, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    Memos, report. Includes Wib Justi.
  - Grange Background, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, pamphlet.
  - Grange Building, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 4 (a-d))
    News clipping, report, articles, correspondence, memos, Bill, releases, draft.
  - New Grange Building, 1957-1960 (Box 22, Folder 5 (a-d))
    News clipping, memos, agreement, correspondence, calculation, redraft, newsletters, article, mats, plans, notebook.
  - Grange Information, 1957-1961 (Box 22, Folder 6 (a-d))
    Correspondence, news clippings, essay. Includes James C. Farmer.
  - Grange Leaders' Conference, 1956-1958 (Box 22, Folder 7 (a-e))
    Correspondence, minutes, outline, script, programs, reference files.
  - Grange Leaders' Conferences, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 8 (a-g))
    Outline, programs, correspondence, memos, news clippings, summary of talk.
  - Grange News 1958, 1957, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 9 (a-h))
    Newsletters, notes, schedule.
  - "Grange News" etc. and Covering Letters, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 10 (a-n))
    Correspondence, statements, address, news releases, form letters, enclosures.
  - "Grange News" etc. and Covering Letters, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 11 (a-e))
    Correspondence, newsletters, statement, address, memo.
  - Holmore Productions, 1957, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, outline, proposal. Includes William G. Rolley, Margaret (Mrs. Harry B.) Caldwell, Charles Holmes, Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc., North Carolina State Grange, Holmore Productions, Inc.
  - Holter, Edward F., 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 13 (a-f))
    Notes, report, Chronology of American Agriculture, pamphlets, handbook, correspondence, forms, article, draft, memos.
  - Inter-Office Memos, 1959, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 14 (a-d))
  - Inter-Farm Organization Meetings, 1957, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Draft, correspondence, notes, agenda, progress.
  - Jackson's Material, 1957, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    Statements, outline of address, correspondence, memo, speech draft.
  - Joint Farm Organization Public Relations Committee, 1959, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, memos, minutes, notes, news clipping. Includes Woodrow Luttrell, American Farm Bureau Federation.
  - Wib Justi, 1959, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    Lists, form, memo, report, drafts of guide. Includes National Grange Youth Program.
  - Mat List 1958, 1956, 1958, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 19 (a-d))
    Mats, newsprint screens (?), forms, newsletters, memos, correspondence, articles. Includes Alberto Salinas Ramos, Asociacion National de Cosecheros.
  - National Live Stock and Meat Board - 1957 (Box 23, Folder 1 (a-e))
    Correspondence, reports, testimony, charts, papers, newsletters, news clippings. Includes Carl F. Neumann, Gordon K. Zimmerman, National Grange Research Director.
  - National Live Stock and Meat Board - 1958, 1958, 1959, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 2 (a-i))
    Editorial, article, pamphlets, reports, minutes, publication, paper, memos, notes. Includes Carl F. Newmann.
  - National Live Stock and Meat Board - 1959, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 3 (a-e))
    Correspondence, minutes, reports, newsletters, memo, pamphlet, list. Includes Carl F. Newmann.
  - Builder Grange - Juvenile - lists, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Builder Grange - Pomona - lists, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Builder Grange - State - list, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Builder Grange - Subordinate - lists, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Grange Builder - Deputies - lists, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Grange Builder - Masters - lists, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Grange Builder - Members - lists, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Grange Builder Program - 1959, 1958, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 11 (a-g))
    Memos, carbon, correspondence, drafts, forms. Includes Frank Archer.
  - Grange Builder Program - 1960, 1960, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, forms, drafts, memos, notes. Includes Harry D. Ritchey, Arkansas State Grange.
  - National Grange Committees, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, report, list, memo.
  - National Grange Monthly - 1958, 1957, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 14 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, forms, articles, memo, agenda. Includes Wilber Levering, C. M. Hall, WIBW & WIBW-TV.
  - National Grange Monthly - 1959 (Box 23, Folder 15 (a-e))
    Editorials, articles, correspondence, drafts. Includes C. M. Hall.
  - National Grange Monthly - 1960 (Box 23, Folder 16 (a-e))
    Editorials, articles, drafts, memos, correspondence, photograph. Includes C. M. Hall.
  - National Grange Monthly Conferences, 1958-1960 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    Notes, memos, agenda, newsletter, report.
  - National Grange Monthly Correspondence - 1960, 1958-1960 (Box 23, Folder 18 (a-f))
    Memos, editorials, correspondence, article, newsletter, news clipping, photographs. Includes William Whitsitt, Ursel C. Narver, Harold Stanley, The Sears-Roebuck Foundation, Grange Mutual Life Company, American Dairy Association of New York State.
  - National Juvenile Matron, 1958, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 19 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, newsletters, pamphlets, outline, memo, articles, photographs. Includes Lucile (Mrs. Byron) Frederick.
  - National Association of Television and Radio Farm Directors, 1957, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 20 (a-i))
    Correspondence, suggestions, list, programs, magazine clippings, address, newsletters, checksheet, draft, speech, summary. Includes Jack Timmons, Robert Miller, Frank Atwood, Herb Plambeck, Donald Lerch, D. Lerch, Jr. & Co., Radio Station WHO, Radio Station WTIC.
  - Newsom Releases, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 1 (a-e))
    Statements, addresses, essay, correspondence.
  - H. D. Newsom, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 2 (a-g))
    Correspondence, memos, news clippings, release, pamphlet, biography, statements, article, photograph, lists.
  - Publications Committees, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Memos, correspondence.
  - Safety, 1958, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Memo, correspondence, pamphlet.
  - Safety Council Antidote Chart, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, chart, form. Includes Marjory (Mrs. Don) Begley, El Monte Community Safety Council.
  - Scholarships - State Granges, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Questionnaires, correspondence.
  - Shell Farm Tour, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Includes W. H. Adams.
  - Special Publicity, 1958, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 8 (a, b))
    News clippings, memos, correspondence, releases, newspaper.
  - Tape Recordings, 1958-1960 (Box 24, Folder 9 (a, b))
    Form letters, correspondence, list, statements, scripts.
  - U.S. - Russian Education, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Study report, memo, draft.
  - "Washington Farm Reporter" - newsletters, 1959, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Youth, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    Handbook, notes, correspondence, memos, newsletters, schedules, reports, pamphlets. Includes Wib Justi.
  - Zimmerman, Gordon, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 13 (a, b))
    Correspondence, memos, statements, report, pamphlets. Includes Gordon K. Zimmerman, A. P. O'Shea, Federated Farmers of New Zealand, Inc.
  - State Grange - Alaska, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Includes James W. Wilson.
  - State Grange - Arkansas, 1958-1960 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, news clippings, newsletter, release. Includes Harry D. Ritchey.
  - State Grange - California, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 16 (a, b))
    Correspondence, news clippings, memo, resolution, program. Includes Craig B. Hazlewood, George Sehlmeyer, California Grange News.
  - State Grange - Colorado, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    Programs, correspondence, memos. Includes Henry Christensen.
  - State Grange - Connecticut, 1958-1960 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, address, newspaper, memos. Includes Robert K. Mitchell.
  - State Grange - Delaware, 1958, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Includes Paris C. Kirby.
  - State Grange - Idaho, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, address, report, account.
  - State Grange - Illinois, 1958-1960 (Box 24, Folder 21 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, programs, script, pamphlet. Includes Frank Westerman.
  - State Grange - Indiana, 1958, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, report.
  - State Grange - Iowa, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 23 (a, b))
    Correspondence, statement, news clipping, address. Includes Loren Murphy.
  - State Grange - Kansas, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, memos, newsletter.
  - State Grange - Maine, 1958-1960 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, news clippings. Includes Adelaide Perry, The Grange Herald.
  - State Grange - Maryland, 1958, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 26 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, articles, memos, directory, report. Includes Austin P. Renn.
  - State Grange - Massachusetts, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    Correspondence, memos, report forms, bulletin, newsletter. Includes Arthur F. Thompson.
  - State Grange - Michigan, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    Correspondence, statement. Includes Clarence J. Tinker, Stanley M. Powell, William J. Brake, Michigan Department of Conservation.
  - State Grange - Minnesota, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    Correspondence, script, memos. Includes William B. Pearson, Frank A. Archer.
  - State Grange - Missouri, 1958-1960 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    Correspondence, news clippings. Includes David Wedding.
  - State Grange - Montana, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, addresses.
  - State Grange - Nebraska, 1957-1959 (Box 24, Folder 32 (a, b))
    Correspondence, news clippings, photograph, pamphlet, biography. Includes George A. Spidel.
  - State Grange - New Hampshire, 1958, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, photograph, report, biography. Includes James C. Farmer, George F. Clement.
  - State Grange - New Jersey, 1958-1960 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    Correspondence, resolutions, newsletter, program, paper. Includes Franklin C. Nixon.
  - State Grange - New York, 1932, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    News clippings, release, article, photograph, correspondence, memos, news letter, outline, pamphlets. Includes Leland D. Smith, Fred D. Rumsey.
  - State Grange - North Carolina, 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 36 (a, b))
    Correspondence, notes, pamphlets, study, release, memos, news clippings, article. Includes Margaret F. (Mrs. Harry B.) Caldwell, Harry B. Caldwell.
  - State Grange - Ohio, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, address, pamphlets, memo.
  - State Grange - Oklahoma, 1958-1960 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Newsletter, list, correspondence, telegram.
  - State Grange - Oregon, 1957-1960 (Box 25, Folder 3 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, news clippings, address, program, photograph, memos. Includes Victor Croxton, Ben Buisman, Elmer McClure, Oregon Grange Bulletin.
  - State Grange - Pennsylvania, 1957-1960 (Box 25, Folder 4 (a-d))
    Correspondence, report, memo, evaluation, register, summary, article, news clippings, release. Includes J. Collins McSparran, Howard T. Benning, Susequehanna County Pomona Grange.
  - State Grange - Rhode Island, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, news clipping.
  - State Grange - South Carolina, 1958-1960 (Box 25, Folder 6 (a, b))
    Correspondence, pamphlet, report, memo, newsletter, news clippings, photograph. Includes D. W. Watkins, Raymond L. Willis.
  - State Grange - South Dakota, 1957-1960 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, program, newsletter, news clippings, report. Includes C. Jerome Davis, W. R. Cummings, National Grange.
  - State Grange - Tennessee, 1958-1960 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Draft, correspondence, newsletter, news clipping. Includes Allan W. McComb.
  - State Grange - Texas, 1957-1960 (Box 25, Folder 9 (a, b, c))
    History, paper, statements, memo, correspondence, release, notes. Includes James M. Bender.
  - State Grange - Vermont, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Program, newsletter, proof, memos, correspondence, news clipping.
  - State Grange - Virginia, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Program, newsletter, proof, memos, correspondence, news clipping. Includes Richard D. Chumney, Richmond Agricultural Grange.
  - State Grange - Washington, 1957-1960 (Box 25, Folder 12 (a-d))
    Correspondence, resolution, newsletter, pamphlet, bulletin, address, program, news clipping. Includes Allan R. Johnson, A. Lars Nelson, Ted F. Berry, The Grange News.
  - State Grange - West Virginia, 1957-1959 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, memo, notes. Includes Stella R. Stoneking.
  - State Grange - Wisconsin, 1958, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, outline of address, program. Includes Ted Walton.
  - State Grange - Wyoming, 1958, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    Includes Clarence P. Jones.
  - State Granges - General Information, 1884, 1958-1960 (Box 25, Folder 16 (a-e))
    Address, correspondence, handbook, pamphlets, forms, lists, correspondence, memo.
  - Grange Builder Program - Arkansas, 1960, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 17 (See 23-11, 12))
    Correspondence, reports, invoice. Includes Harry B. Ritchy, Arkansas State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - California, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, reports, invoice. Includes J. B. Quinn, California State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Colorado, 1960, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    Correspondence, memos, invoice, reports. Includes Henry Christensen, Colorado State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Connecticut, 1960, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, lists, reports, invoice. Includes Robert K. Mitchell, Connecticut State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Delaware, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    Correspondence, invoice, reports. Includes Paris C. Kirby, Delaware State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Idaho, 1960, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, invoice, reports. Includes W. E. Adams, Idaho State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Illinois, 1960, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, reports. Includes Dorsey Kirk, Illinois State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Indiana, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, invoice, reports.
  - Grange Builder Program - Iowa, 1960, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, invoice, reports. Includes Loren Murphy, Iowa State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Kansas, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    Correspondence, invoice, reports. Includes Harry C. Colglazier, Kansas State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Maine, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    Correspondence, invoice, report.
  - Grange Builder Program - Maryland, 1960, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    Correspondence, invoices, reports. Includes Austin P. Renn, Maryland State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Massachusetts, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    Correspondence, invoice, reports. Includes Arthur F. Thompson, Massachusetts State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Michigan, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    Correspondence, report, invoice. Includes W. J. Brake, Michigan State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Minnesota, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, reports. Includes William B. Pearson, Minnesota State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Missouri, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Grange Builder Program - Montana, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, reports, invoice. Includes Winton Weydemeyer, Montana State Grange.
  - Grange Builder Program - Nebraska, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    Correspondence, reports, invoice.
  - Grange Builder Program - New Hampshire, 1960, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Grange Builder Program - New Jersey, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Grange Builder Program - New York, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Grange Builder Program - North Carolina, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    Correspondnece, invoice, reports.
  - Grange Builder Program - Ohio, Oklahoma, Oregon, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, South Carolina, South Dakota, Tennessee, Texas, Vermont, Virginia, Washington, W. Virginia, Wisconsin, Wyoming, 1960, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 39-53)
    Correspondence, invoices, reports.
- Series X. Director of Youth Activities, Wib Justi
  - DYA "staff", 1958-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Notes, correspondence, memos. Includes Harry Graham, Cornell Grange.
  - DYA - Staff Meeting Memo, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Memo - Sharlach, JoAnne, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Committee - Advisory Committee on Young Workers, 1959-1963 (Box 26, Folder 4 (a-d))
    Correspondence, memos, agenda, summary list, pamphlets, draft, statement. Includes Bureau of Labor Standards, U.S. Department of Labor.
  - Committee - Advisory Safety Committee on Farm Employed Youth - Information Folder, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Committee - Agricultural Chemical Safety, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Memos, report.
  - Committee - Auto Safety Foundation, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Note, correspondence.
  - Committees - Boy Scouts of America, 1959, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, minutes, list, report.
  - Committees - Council of National Organizations for Children and Youth, 1950, 1958-1964 (Box 26, Folder 9 (a-d))
    Correspondence, reports, minutes, ballot, form, evaluation, list, memos.
  - Committee - Council on Student Travel, 1960-1963 (Box 26, Folder 10 (a-d))
    Note, memo, agenda, minutes, bulletins, reports.
  - Committee - Farm Film Foundation, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Note, memo, pamphlet.
  - Committee - (Advisory) Farm Safety, U.S. Department of Labor, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, note, agenda.
  - Committee - National Folk Festival Association, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Correspondence, note, memo.
  - National Planning and Advisory Committee, 1951-1953 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, report, proposal, outlines. Includes H. O. Stuart, National 4-H Committee.
  - Committee - National Safety Council, 1962, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, minutes, program. Includes Harold E. Heldreth, Youth Activities Department.
  - National Youth Committee 1956 - Correspondence, 1952, 1953, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - National Youth Committee 1958-1959 - Memo (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - National Youth Committee - General, 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 18 (a, b))
    Memos, reports, summary.
  - Memos - Smith, Mary, 1963-1966 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Committees - People-to-People, 1958-1963 (Box 26, Folder 20 (a, b))
    Correspondence, minutes, reports, reprints, minutes. Includes Allan B. Kline, People-to-People Farm Committee.
  - Committees - Rural Youth Leaders, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    Lists, memo.
  - Special Advisory Committee for the 1964 Census of Agriculture, 1963, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 22 (a, b, c))
    Correspondence, minutes, suggestions, agenda, questionnaire. Includes Ray Hurley, Agriculture Division, Bureau of the Census, U.S. Department of Commerce.
  - Committee - Visit USA - 1960 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, memo, report.
  - Committee - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1960, 1961, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, minutes, memo.
  - Committee - Youth Activities Conference [former Youth Service Committee], 1963, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, minutes, questionnaire. Includes Harold E. Heldreth.
  - Youth Service Committee, 1961, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 26 (a-f))
    Correspondence, summary, program, reports, agenda, minutes. Includes Harold E. Heldreth.
  - Youth Service Committee Annual Meeting - Oct. 15, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    Prepared notebook.
  - Grange - 4-H General, 1969-1961 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    Correspondence, notes, entry form, newsletter.
  - Grange - 4-H Club Recognition 1958-1959 (Box 26, Folder 29 (a, b))
    Correspondence, entries with photos and news clippings.
  - Grange - 4-H Club Recognition 1959-1960, 1960, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 30 (a-e))
    Correspondence, entries with photos and news clippings, list.
  - Grange - Peace Corps Administration - Activities Fund, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    Correspondence, memo.
  - GPC - Adm. Applicants - questionnaire, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - GPC - Adm. - Contracts, 1965, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - GPC - Adm. - Contractor's Overseas Representative, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    Correspondence, memo, application. Includes John Earl Hutchinson, Mary Ellen Hutchinson.
  - GPC - ADM. - COR candidates, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    Memo, applications. Includes Conn Price, John Ralph Nichols.
  - GPC - Adm. - Salaries, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    Correspondence, note. Includes T. James Goering, W. P. Kelly, Director of Contracts and Logistics, Peace Corps.